{
	"data": [
    {
      "question": "Jennifer got up ___ miss the bus.",
      "a": "so early to",
      "b": "early as to",
      "c": "so early not as to",
      "d": "so early as not to",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "- So + adj/adv + as + to/not to",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Of the two toys, the child chose ___.",
      "a": "the one most beautiful",
      "b": "the less beautiful",
      "c": "the most beautiful of them",
      "d": "the least beautiful",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "- The less beautiful (one of two boys)",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "If a customer had to choose between the two products, he/she would say the one of high quality was _________ choice.",
      "a": "the best",
      "b": "good",
      "c": "the better",
      "d": "better",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "- The better choice (between two)",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Judy is _________ of the two girls.",
      "a": "much more active",
      "b": "more active",
      "c": "the most active",
      "d": "the more active",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "- the more active (between two)Â ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The teacher in white is ___ of the two.",
      "a": "handsomest",
      "b": "handsomer",
      "c": "the handsomest",
      "d": "the handsomer",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "- the handsomer (between two)",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The bride was ___ moved _________ speak.",
      "a": "too, to",
      "b": "very, to",
      "c": "so, that",
      "d": "enough, to",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- too + adj + to",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The blouse and the skirt are ___ nice. ___ I look at them, ___ I want to buy them.",
      "a": "very, Best, best",
      "b": "much, More, the more",
      "c": "much very, More, less",
      "d": "very, The more, the more",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "- the more .... the more",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The _________ an object is from us, the ___ it looks.",
      "a": "further away, smaller",
      "b": "farther away, less",
      "c": "farthest away, smallest",
      "d": "farther away, smaller",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "- The + adj -er ..... the + adj -er",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "It's believed that ___ one works, ___ result one will get.",
      "a": "the more hard, the more better",
      "b": "the harder, the better",
      "c": "more hard, more better",
      "d": "the harder, a better",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "- The + adj - er ..... the + adj - er",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The more I look at the tie, ___.",
      "a": "the less I like it",
      "b": "the better I liked",
      "c": "better it I like",
      "d": "I like it less",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- The + adj -er ..... The + adj -er",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    }
  ]
}